《黑镜》
《绞死DJ》
- 指导 - 请说 弗兰克
- Coach. - Yes, Frank?
- 我去哪 - 前往中心
- Where do I go? - Proceed to the hub.
好的
Got ya.
- 我怎么知道哪个是他 - 是这个
- How will I know who he is? - This is him.
抱歉 叉子
Sorry. Fork.
- 艾米 - 不不 我不叫叉子
- Amy. - No, no, my name's not fork.
- 我知道 就是… - 我叫弗兰克
- I guessed. It was just… - It's Frank.
要坐下吗
Do you wanna sit?
- 我们坐下吗 - 要不只能站着了
- Shall we sit? - I think it's that or stand.
坐吧
Come sit, yeah?
我…坐那边的
That's, um… I was on that side.
- 那我… - 不不 没事的
- Shall I…? - No, no, it doesn't matter.
我真是多嘴
Why bring it up?
抱歉 我太紧张了
Sorry. I'm so bloody nervous.
我第一次使用…系统
It's my first time on the, you know, the system.
- 我也是 - 真的
- Me too. - Oh, really?
是啊 我要吓尿了
Yeah, I'm shitting it, mate.
- 说起来 你看上去是吓坏了 - 是吗
- Come to mention it, you look terrified. - Do I?
是啊 怕得打颤
Yeah, quaking with fear.
或是因为反感而颤抖
Or maybe shaking with revulsion?
至少你不…尿了
At least you stopped… shitting.
你确定吗
Are you sure about that?
我们别再谈尿了吧
Shall we stop talking about shitting?
点个餐什么的 好主意
Maybe order some food? Good plan.
是啊 好吧
Yeah. OK.
- 知道我们怎么点吗 - 应该是用这个
- Do you know how we order? - I think we use these.
菜单已经订好
Menu choice already established.
- 请慢用 先生 - 谢谢
- Here you are, sir. - Ta.
还有您的 女士
And for you, madam.
看来 我喜欢意大利面
Well, evidently I'm a pasta girl.
是啊 我是
Yeah, I'm a, uh…
鱼饼…
…fishcake…
- 挺好吃的 - 我能尝尝吗
- It's good. - Can I try some?
那样 可以吗
Are we… allowed to do that?
管他呢
Fuck it.
是啊 管他呢
Yeah, fuck it.
真好吃
That is good.
那么 我们都是第一次的
So… we're both first-timers.
看看我们的有效期吧
Shall we check our expiry date?
- 好主意 - 好吗
- Yeah, good plan. - Yeah?
好 应该是在「信息」里看
All right, um, so I think it's under "info."
嗯 「按下显示」
Yeah, uh, "tap to reveal."
我们得同时按
We have to tap to reveal at the same time.
好 那么 倒数 三
OK. So, on three,
二 一 按下
two, one. Go.
- 12小时 - 是啊 12小时
- Twelve hours. - Yeah, 12 hours.
- 好吧 - 有点…
- OK. - Bit, um…
- 是啊 - 有点短
- Yeah. - Bit short.
是有点短 是吧
It is a bit short, isn't it?
还越来越短了 我不知道它还…
And getting shorter. I didn't realize it would…
还这样倒数
sort of count down like that.
好悲哀啊
It's sort of sad.
或许我们该快点吃
Maybe we should eat quickly.
- 是啊 你说得对 - 比赛开始
- Yeah. Yeah, maybe we should. - The race is on.
快点 快吃
Come on, hurry up.
看来是我们了
I guess this is us.
这带我们去那里吗
And this takes us to the place?
应该是的
Yeah, suppose so.
- 你先请 - 谢谢
- After you. - Thank you.
好大啊
It's massive.
- 我们到了 - 是啊
- Here we are. - Yep.
- 你想来开吗 还是我来 - 你来吧
- Do you wanna open it or shall I? - You go ahead.
好
All right.
太慢了
Too slow.
你好傻
You're a knob.
天啊 里面好烂
Oh, God. It's a shithole.
- 你开玩笑的吧 - 是啊
- You're kidding. - I am, yeah.
不错啊 我喜欢这灯
It's nice. I, uh, like that lamp.
- 是啊 那灯真不错 - 少来了
- Yeah, it's incredible, that lamp. - Fuck off.
好吧
Right.
那是…
That's, uh…
还有套件
There's an en suite.
- 淋浴还是浴盆 - 都有
- Shower or bath? - Both.
真不错
That's good.
我用下厕所
Well, I'm… I'm just gonna use the loo.
嗯 我也得…在这里…
Yeah, I've got to, uh… over here, so…
嗯
Yeah.
好吧 说真的 我们该做什么啊
OK, seriously, what are we meant to do?
问题太宽泛 请缩小范围
Query too broad. Please narrow.
我是说 我们要…
Well, I mean, are we just meant to…
开干吗
I don't know, like, just go at it?
请定义「开干」
Define "go at it."
我去
Fucking hell.
我们是要一起做爱吗
So, are we meant to just have sex with each other?
并不要求参与者必须采取什么指定行动
Participants are not required to take any specific action.
是啊 但我们可以这么做吧
Yeah, but I mean we can, right?
如果时间很短 有人会这么做吧
I mean, people do if it's just a short time?
如果你们决定如此
If that's your decision.
- 这由我们决定 - 由你们决定
- It's up to us? - It's up to you.
我可以睡这儿
I could just sleep here.
别傻了 那样腿都伸不开
Don't be daft. You'll be scrunched up in a ball.
没那么差的
It's not awful.
床挺大的 我觉得咱俩都躺得下的
The bed's pretty big. I'm sure we could both fit in it.
那好
Yeah, OK.
有系统之前肯定很疯狂吧
Must have been mental before the system.
什么意思
How do you mean?
人们还得自己去恋爱
Well, people had to do the whole relationship thing themselves,
搞清楚自己想跟谁在一起
work out who they wanna be with.
选择无力
Option paralysis.
选择太多 你反而不知道自己想要什么了
So many choices, you end up not knowing which one you want.
是啊 没错 如果情况不妙
Yeah, exactly, and if things seem shitty,
他们还得考虑
they'd have to figure out.
自己要不要跟人分手
whether they wanted to break up with someone.
怎么跟人分手啊 老天爷
How to break up with someone. Fuckin' hell.
- 真是噩梦 - 不像安排好了时那样
- Just a nightmare. - It's not like when it's all mapped out.
可不是 安排好了简单多了
God, no. It's so much simpler when it's all mapped out.
- 但这样好怪 - 是啊
- This is weird, though. - It really is.
那么
Well, then.
So…
谢谢你做我的第一个
Thanks for being my first.
该死的时间
Bloody time.
感觉很棒 你真的很棒
It was great, you know. You were nice.
你也是
So were you.
如果我们还能有这个时间 你绝对能上了我
If we had this time again, you would totally get it, by the way.
- 你…坏死了 - 抱歉
- You… You bastard. - Sorry.
- 你也是 - 我们真是搞砸了 是吧
- You'd get it, too. - Fucked that one up, didn't we?
是啊
Yeah, totally.
我就是觉得时间那么短没什么意义
I guess I just don't see the point in something that short.
才12小时
Twelve hours.
你对短暂邂逅的反应
Even your reaction to a brief encounter.
也向系统提供了宝贵信息
provides the system with valuable information.
是啊 我什么都没做呢
Yeah, well, I didn't even do anything.
系统觉得我是个假正经
The system thinks I'm a prude.
系统不做任何道德评判
The system makes no moral judgments.
但我怎么知道她不是我的完美伴侣
Yeah, but how do I know she wasn't the perfect match for me?
她…
I mean, she was…
你的绝配尚未被选定
Your ultimate compatible other has not yet been selected.
我知道 但是…
Yeah, I know, but it's…
系统通过每位参与者与数个对象
The system gains insight as each participant.
交往的过程增进了解
progresses through numerous relationships.
并用所采集的数据
and uses the gathered data.
来最终选定绝配
to eventually select an ultimate compatible other.
在配对日 我知道
On your pairing day, I know,
它总能找到你的完美对象
and it always finds your perfect match.
在99.8%的案例中 是的
In 99.8% of cases.
但我得经历一大堆恋爱才能找到
But I have to go through loads of relationships to find it.
- 没错 - 太好了
- That is correct. - Great.
那是什么
What was that?
- 新的恋爱 - 这么快
- Another relationship. - What, already?
这是什么 又来一个
What's this, another one?
是的
That is correct.
那我该去换衣服了
I'd best go get changed, then.
我去 那是他吧
Holy fuck. Tell me that's him.
我只能在个人介绍后确认身份
I cannot confirm identity until a personal introduction is made.
身份确认
Identity confirmed.
- 我喜欢你的头发 - 你的也不错
- I like your hair. - Yours is good too.
可是我自己的
It's all my own.
太逗了
It's just funny.
我是弗兰克
I'm Frank.
妮可拉
Nicola.
我到了有一会儿了
I've been here a while.
抱歉 我去换衣服来着
Aye, sorry. I was getting changed.
- 真的 - 你已经开始了
- Really? - You started already?
- 我饿了 - 当然 抱歉
- I was hungry. - Yeah, course, yeah. Sorry.
赶紧的吧 看看有效期
Come on, let's get it over with. Checking the expiry.
好啊
Yeah, yeah.
一年
One year.
我们可以交往一年 是不是搞错了
We've got each other for one year? Could be a mistake.
- 指导 是不是搞错了 - 不是搞错了
- Coach, is this a mistake? - This is not a mistake.
老天爷啊
Jesus fucking Christ.
肯定有原因的
There'll be a reason.
谢谢
Thanks.
想想好的一面 咖喱鸡
Look on the bright side. Chicken tikka masala.
什么
What?
咖喱鸡 是个玩笑
Chicken tikka mas… It's a joke.
哦
Right.
那么你还开玩笑
So you're the sort of person that makes jokes.
- 好吧 倒数三 - 二 一
- OK, so on three. - Two, one.
有意思
Interesting.
九个月
Nine months.
好吧
Well…
干杯
cheers.
Cheers.
跟我上一个差不多
Pretty much the same as my last one.
你做过几次了
How many of these have you had?
恋爱吗 到目前 五个
Relationships? So far? Five.
我算是老手了吧
I'm an old hand, I suppose.
那个 我去冲个澡
Listen, I'm just gonna jump in the shower.
- 好 - 不会要很久的
- OK. - Won't be long.
听着 如果你不介意
So, listen, if you're OK with it,
这是我第五次恋爱了
this is relationship five for me,
我发觉最好是直接就开始做爱
and I've found it's best to have sex straight away upfront.
是嘛
Right, yeah.
可以打破尴尬
Kind of breaks the ice,
对匹配性有个比较早的大致了解
gives an early overview of compatibility and so on.
嗯
Yep.
那么我这就同意一切
So I'm consenting to everything now.
你什么时候愿意也这么做
Whenever you feel comfortable doing the same…
咖喱…
Tikka masala. Just…
- 什么 - 有点咖喱味儿
- What? - It's a bit tikka masala.
- 抱歉 - 你说话时更重了
- I'm sorry. - Talking makes it worse.
抱歉
Sorry.
不不 你得从后面来了
No, no, you're gonna have to do it from behind.
- 什么 - 从后面来
- You what? - From behind.
再快点
Bit faster?
多点动作
More motion.
不是那样 多点动作 你就进进出出的
Not like that. More motion. You're all in out, in out,
好像是想关上文件柜的抽屉
like you're trying to shut a drawer into a filing cabinet.
- 抱歉 - 太无聊了
- Sorry. - It's just boring.
多点横向动作
Want a bit more side to side.
这样吗
Like this?
不是的
No, not really.
怎么了
What was that?
没事
Nothing.
（365天）
我去啊
Fucking hell.
我不能直接退出吗
So I can't just walk away?
是的
That is correct.
它最终会为你找到绝配
One day it will provide you with the ultimate match.
最终 最终
One day. One day.
我想说
So I'd just like to say,
要相信系统 它能够兑现承诺
do have faith in the system, because it does deliver.
对我们就是的
It did for us.
你会积累很多经验
You have so many experiences,
最终有一天 它为你找到绝配
and then one day it pairs you up with your ultimate match,
这里最好的
the best in show, as it were.
如果你有所怀疑 要坚持下来
So if you're having doubts, just hang on in there.
因为它真的好使
Because it really does work.
蒜酱汁 多谢了
Garlic dip. Thanks for that.
你好啊
You all right.
那是你的…
Was that, uh, your…?
- 是啊 妮可拉 - 妮可拉
- Yeah. Nicola. - Oh. Nicola.
你没事吧
You OK?
你不是…你真的假的啊
No, you're not being…? Are you being serious?
上帝 还是来真的 好吧
Oh, my God. OK, this is happening. OK, um, just…
谢谢
Thanks.
- 你好美 - 谢谢
- You look well. - Thanks.
我倒想也赞美你两句
I'd return the compliment,
但你刚把食物吐在了我鞋上
but you've just spat food on my shoe, so…
不过老实说 那鞋很恶心
To be fair, it is a revolting shoe, so…
那正好用来踢你了
All the better to kick you with.
很疼吗
Was that really hard?
- 疼啊 - 真抱歉 该死
- Ouch. - I'm so sorry. Fuck.
该死
Shit.
兰尼 这是弗兰克 弗兰克 这是兰尼
Lenny, this is, um, Frank. Frank, this is Lenny.
兰尼 你好啊
Hi, Lenny. You all right?
我们在一起过一小段时间
We were together for a bit.
- 很小的一段时间 - 是啊 在我们之前
- A small… small bit. - Yeah, just before we…
你俩是…那太好了
So you two…? Oh. That's… that's great.
你俩看上去很般配
So, I mean… it looks like you two make a great team.
是啊
Yeah.
- 嗯 - 回见了
- Yeah. - Um, I'll see you.
嗯
Yeah.
- 你知道你发出的那个声音 - 什么声音
- You know that noise you make? - What noise?
我有吗
Do I do that?
有的 经常的
Yeah, you do, quite often.
让你烦吗
Does it bother you?
有点 是的
A bit, yeah.
- 我尽量不弄了 - 好
- I'll try not to. - OK.
（5个月）
（2个月）
（7周）
（3周）
（17秒）
（16秒）
（15秒）
我真的很开心
So it's been great, really.
- 可惜要结束了 - 但也没办法
- Shame it has to end. - But end it must.
总之
Anyway…
好 再见
OK, bye.
这就又有新伴侣了
Another partner already?
是的
That is correct.
好 三 二 一 按
So, three, two, one, go.
（36小时）
36小时
Thirty-six hours?
好 再见
Well, uh… bye.
- 再见 - 再见
- Bye. - Bye.
三 二 一
Three, two, one.
（36小时）
（结束）
- 我想说 - 别了
- I just wanna say… - Don't.
我现在知道跟我讨厌的人一起生活的滋味了
Well, I learned what it's like to cohabit with someone I despise.
这对系统有帮助吗
Is that useful for the system?
一切皆有原因
Everything happens for a reason.
比我想的要快啊
That's sooner than I expected.
你好啊
Hello, you.
这没错吗
Is this right?
- 是啊 - 我是说…
- Yeah. - I mean…
我没想到系统会让我们再约会
Yeah, I didn't think the system would hook us up again.
我也是
No, me neither.
我当然希望是没搞错 但是…
I mean, I hope it's right, obviously, but…
指导 我们没坐错桌子吧
Coach, are we sat at the right table?
没坐错
Yes, that is correct.
那好吧
OK, well…
等等 我们先别看有效期了
Wait, um… Can we not check the expiry date?
- 为什么 - 我好烦那个
- Why? - Just sick of it.
系统让我一个个人地换
The system's just bounced me from bloke to bloke,
全是露水情缘
short fling after short fling.
我知道那都是露水情缘 毫无意义
I know they're short flings, they're just meaningless,
我心不在焉 完全不在状态
and I get really detached. It's like I'm not really there.
那一周 我跟一个人在一起
So the other week, I was with this guy,
天知道是谁 就是换了张脸
God knows who, basically just a haircut.
我真有种灵魂出窍的感觉
And I literally had this out-of-body experience.
我的魂魄飞了出去
I wandered out of my body,
坐在了房间对面的椅子上
and I sat in this chair across the room.
看着自己干那男的
and I watched myself fucking this guy.
我就想 这怎么回事啊
And I was, like, what is that all about?
那完全就是一根屌进进出出地插一个洞
That is literally just a dick going in and out of a hole.
是啊 是挺不走心的
Yeah, that's pretty detached.
但是长期的恋爱也一样糟糕
When it's a long-term thing, it's just as bad,
简直像蹲监狱一样等着时间过去
watching the clock like you're a prisoner,
每分钟 每小时地数着
counting the hours, the minutes.
- 天啊 深有体会 - 是啊
- Oh, God, I've been there. - Yeah.
- 是啊 我们别看有效期了 - 好
- Yeah, let's not check the expiry, then. - Yeah.
- 说定了 - 说定了
- It's a deal. - Deal.
好
OK.
上鱼饼吧
Bring on les fishcake.
我也不知道
I don't know.
- 怎么样 - 那么
- So? - So…
- 不如就做吧 - 我想我们必须做
- Might as well. - I suppose we have to.
不知道我们有多少时间
Don't know how much time we've got.
可能是10分钟呢
Yeah, it could be ten minutes.
- 你觉得你能坚持10分钟吗 - 讨厌
- Think you could last ten minutes? - Fuck off.
那好吧
All right. OK, then.
等等 我们中该有一个人先脱衣服
Wait. One of us should get undressed first.
- 为什么就一个 - 那样多好玩
- Why only one of us? - It'll be funny.
来吧 脱裤子吧
Go on then. Get your kit off.
不不 是我的点子
No. No, it was my idea.
好吧
All right.
这样让我好没面子
This is kind of emasculating.
那你待会儿可得大展雄风
Well, then, you'd better make up for it in a minute.
我要看你的老二
I'm gonna see your dick.
抱歉
Sorry.
- 我要看到它啦 - 行啦
- I'm gonna fucking see it - Yeah, OK. Yeah…
要是根本没有审查呢
What if there is no scrutiny,
只是把我们随机地配对
it's just putting us together in any old order,
我们都听之任之
and we all go along with it.
因为他们总在宣传这个系统多智能
'cause they're always telling us how clever it is?
是啊 但它能让人们找到真爱
Yeah, but it does put people with the one.
有99.8%的成功率呢
It's got a 99.8% success rate.
但你怎么知道他们是完美匹配的
But how do you know they're perfect matches?
如果它其实只是在
I mean, what if all it's actually doing.
渐渐消磨我们的耐心
is gradually wearing us down,
让我们经历一段段的恋情
putting us in one relationship after another.
以随机的顺序 时长也是随机的
for random durations in a random sequence?
每次 你都会变得更顺从
Each time you get a little bit more pliable,
更心碎一点
a little bit more broken,
直到最终 它给出最终提议
until eventually it coughs up the final offering.
并告诉你那就是完美对象
and says that's the one.
到那时 你已经太挫败 太疲惫
And by that point you are so defeated and so exhausted.
你直接接受了 将就了
that you just accept it, you settle.
然后 你余生都得一直
And then you have to live the rest of your life.
说服自己 那不是将就
convincing yourself you didn't.
说得好 真是我听过的最阴暗的论调了
Well done. That's one of the bleakest things I've ever heard.
谢谢
Thank you.
好了 你想听听我的理论吗
Right. Do you wanna know my theory?
假设系统不是随机的
Let's assume the system isn't random.
- 是真如他们说的那么复杂 - 好
- It's as sophisticated as they say it is. - OK.
嗯 它用这个捕捉你的所有反应 是吧
Right, so using these, it slurps up all your reactions, yeah?
建立一个复杂的档案
It builds up a complex profile.
你每一个疯狂的念头
Every crazy thought you've ever had,
你所有的梦想和弱点
all your dreams and your weaknesses and…
- 你的疯狂理论是 - 你脑海里的一切
- And your mad theories. - Yeah, like, everything in your head.
如果是你脑袋里的一切
Right. So if it's everything in your head…
- 那它有思想吗 - 好吧 那么你是要说
- does it have thoughts? - All right, so now you're gonna say:
「如果那就是我们 我们困在模拟里了呢」
"What if that's us and we're stuck in a simulation?"
我们要怎么知道呢
Well, how would we know?
这不就知道了
I think that settles it.
我可能被编程了要喊疼呢
I might have been programmed to go "Ow."
好吧
Ok.
- 过来 - 不
- Come here. - No.
- 指导 - 你好 弗兰克
- Coach? - Hello, Frank.
- 我必须知道 - 你想知道什么
- I've gotta know. - What would you like to know?
我和艾米的有效期 我需要知道有多久
The expiry date for me and Amy. I need to know how long.
你不打算劝我别问吗
You're not gonna talk me out of it?
你希望我劝你别问吗
Would you like me to talk you out of it?
嗯 不 我…
Yeah. Uh… No. I…
我不知道
Don't know.
（按下显示 双方必须同时按下）
不 我不做了 我说过不做的
No, I'm not gonna do it. I said I wouldn't.
我们还握手了
We shook on it.
不管了
Fuck it.
（5年）
重新校准
Recalibrating.
（3年）
指导
Coach?
- 指导 - 重新校准
- Coach. - Recalibrating.
指导 怎么回事 指导 越来越短了
Coach. What's happening? Coach, it's getting shorter.
单向查看让有效期不稳定了
One-sided observation has destabilized the expiry date.
- 什么 - 单向查看
- What? - One-sided observation.
让有效期不稳定了
has destabilized the expiry date.
重新校准
Recalibrating.
因为我自己看了 所以它越来越短了
'Cause I looked at it on my own, it made it shorter?
- 是的 - 为什么
- That is correct. - Why?
一切皆有原因
Everything happens for a reason.
好吧 那撤销 让它倒回去
All right, well, undo it, then. Make it go back.
我做不到 重新校准
I cannot do that. Recalibrating.
要是她也看呢
What if she looks at it?
一旦缩短 有效期就不能再延长
Once shortened, the expiry date cannot be extended.
为什么
Why?
一切皆有原因
Everything happens for a reason.
- 别这样 - 重新校准
- Come on. Come on. - Recalibrating.
- 它什么时候停下来 - 重新校准
- When will it stop? - It will stabilize.
结束后便会稳定下来 重新校准
once recalibration has completed. Recalibrating.
停下 停下啊
Stop it. Stop it. Just…
你没事吧
You OK?
嗯 我没事
Yeah, I'm fine.
- 好吧 - 我很好
- All right. - I'm good.
你打出过超过四下或低于四下的吗
Have you ever had more than four or less than four?
你想什么呢
What you thinking about?
没事
Nothing.
好吧 说真的 怎么了
All right, seriously, what's up?
我看了
I looked.
看了什么
Looked at what?
我们说好不看的 我们还握手了
We promised we wouldn't. We shook on it.
你不想知道是多少吗
Don't you wanna know what it said?
不想 就是因为不想
No. That was the point.
- 反正也快结束了 - 差多久
- It's almost done anyway. - How almost done?
我们就剩一小时了
We've got, like, an hour.
你为什么不早点说
Why didn't you tell me this before?
- 不想破坏气氛 - 这就不破坏了吗
- Didn't wanna spoil today. - And this hasn't spoilt it?
本来是五年的 但现在
It was supposed to be five years, but now…
我看了 结果出事了 它开始缩短
I looked at it, something happened, it started going down.
- 我不知道怎么回事 - 是你弄坏了
- I don't know what it was. - So you broke it?
不是的 我也不知道
No, no, no, no, no. I mean, I don't… I don't know.
你为什么非要看
Why did you have to look at it?
我在想 或许我们可以想办法绕过它
Look, I was thinking maybe we could overcome it somehow.
你为什么非要看
Why did you have to look at it?
因为我喜欢你
Because I like you.
我真的喜欢你
Like properly, really, I like you.
老天爷啊 那就不够吗
For fuck's sake. And that wasn't enough?
那不是重点
That's not the point.
我看了 但那不是重点
I looked, but that's not the issue here.
你确定吗
Are you sure about that?
搞什么 你对这个比对没多少时间了
What the fuck! You're more wound up about that.
更生气
than how short the time is.
是啊 因为我们说好的
Yes, because we had agreed.
听我说
Listen. Listen. Listen.
- 如果我们不管它呢 - 我们不能
- What if we just ignore it? - We can't.
听我说 我们不管系统了
Listen, we'll just fuck the system. We'll fuck it…
- 然后呢 - 跳出去 跳到墙外面去
- And do what? - We'll jump out, over the wall, get out.
外面什么都没有
There is nothing out there.
你怎么知道 你怎么知道
How d'you know? How d'you know?
- 艾米 - 你给毁了
- Amy… - You've ruined this.
你给毁了
You've ruined it.
没事的
Hey, it's nothing.
- 艾米 - 别跟我来
- Amy. - Don't follow me.
艾米 对不起
Amy, I'm sorry.
艾米
Amy.
- 一切皆有原因 - 什么原因
- Everything happens for a reason. - What reason?
系统将评估你对一段
The system will be assessing your reaction.
珍视感情的过早结束的反应
to the painful premature termination of a treasured relationship.
并据此改进它对
and will adjust and improve its profile.
最终真爱的解析
of your eventual chosen one accordingly.
- 你真会安慰人 - 谢谢
- You're a great comfort. - Thank you.
我发誓 我现在想翻过外面那座墙
I swear to God, I feel like scaling the wall out there.
跳进荒野里
and jumping in the fucking wilderness.
那会违反系统规则
That would contravene the rules of the system.
去他妈的系统
The fucking system.
不遵守系统规则可能会被驱逐
Failure to comply with the system may result in banishment.
我知道了
All right, I know.
老天 你就不能让我发发火吗 不行吗
Christ, will you let me be angry at least? Will you give me that?
有效期截止时 你必须搬出
You must vacate your current living quarters.
现在的居所
when the time expires.
好像我不知道似的
Like I didn't know.
要是我没看 我们还能在一起好几年
And if I hadn't have looked, we'd have been together years.
她…
She was…
你知道当你遇到了一个人 你立刻就知道了
You know when you meet someone and you just know?
你立刻知道…
You just know that…
你现在能插我了吗 我下巴都疼了
Reckon you could pop this in me now? I've sort of got jaw ache.
嗯 来吧
Yeah, come on.
发生了那一切
And after all that,
他都没道过歉 一次都没有
he never even apologized, not once.
太糟了
That's too bad.
你介意我想着她吗
Do you mind if I think about her?
我可以想着他吗
If I can think about him?
嗯 好
Yeah, sound.
一 二 三 四
One, two, three, four.
恭喜 艾米
Congratulations, Amy.
你的绝配已经找到
Your ultimate match has been identified.
你的配对日是明天
Your pairing day is tomorrow.
- 绝配 「真爱」吗 - 是的
- Ultimate as in "The one"? - That is correct.
- 我们明天见面 - 是的
- And we meet tomorrow? - That is correct.
明天 你将与你的绝配配对
Tomorrow you'll be coupled with your ultimate match.
你们将一起永远离开这里
and together you will leave this place forever.
好的
Ok.
你可以跟我说说那人吗
Are you allowed to tell me anything about them?
- 我已经认识那人了吗 - 不
- Do I know them already? - Negative.
- 这样啊 - 还有件事
- Right. - There is one more thing.
怎么了
Yeah, and what's that?
配对日之前
Prior to pairing day,
你可以获得短暂的告别时间
you have been allocated a short farewell period.
对象你可以自己选择
with an individual of your choosing.
告别时间 就是我可以跟一个人告别吗
A farewell period? Like, I get to say goodbye to someone?
是的
That is correct.
数据显示这可以提供心理上的了结
Data shows this can help provide psychological closure.
弗兰克 我选择弗兰克
Frank, I choose Frank.
你的选择已经登记
Your choice has been registered.
等等 我们要在哪见面
Wait. Where are we meeting?
老地方 晚上7：30
Usual booth, 7:30 p.m.
好
Right.
- 指导 - 艾米 请说
- Coach? - Yes, Amy?
数到四
Count to four.
一 二 三 四
One, two, three, four.
等等 我们有多久
Wait, wait. How long have we got?
系统把我的配对日安排在了明天
Look, the system's set my pairing day for tomorrow.
- 我也是 - 好
- Yeah, me too. - Right.
我不想要系统给我选的人 好吗
I don't want whoever the system reckons the one is, OK?
- 我想要你 - 我也想要你
- I want you. - I want you.
不遵守系统规则
Failure to comply with the system.
- 可能会被驱逐 - 你滚边吧
- may result in banishment. - You can fuck off.
你记得你来之前在哪吗
Can you remember where you were before you came here?
你记不得 是吧
You can't, can you?
- 不能 - 我也是
- No. - Me neither.
- 我为什么记不得 - 这是测试
- Why can't I think of that? - It's a test.
你记得我们在一起的第一晚吗
Do you remember the first night that we were together?
那第一晚 你有什么感觉
I mean the first night. How did you feel?
感觉安全 开心 舒服
I felt safe, happy, comfortable.
感觉很对
It felt right.
感觉有什么正合适
It felt like something locked into place, you know,
像是我们认识
like we'd met before.
感觉似曾相识 还会再发生
Like it had happened before and it'll happen again,
感觉好像已经发生了数千次
like it's happened a thousand times over and over again.
- 你明白我的意思吗 - 我明白
- Do you know what I mean? - Yeah. Yeah, I do.
自从我们认识 这世界就在玩弄我们
Ever since we've met, this world has been toying with us.
想拆散我们
It's trying to keep us apart. It's…
这是个测试 我发誓
It's a test, I swear it is,
我们要一起反叛它
and the two of us rebelling together.
才能通过测试
is something to do with passing it.
我们得推翻一切
We've gotta fuck it all off.
没错 我们要推翻一切规则 逃离这里
Exactly. We've just gotta fuck the whole thing off and go.
- 好 去翻墙 - 没错
- Yeah, over the wall. - Right over it.
- 不管外面是什么 - 好
- No matter what's out there. - OK.
我们走吧
So let's go.
嗯 我们走吧
Yeah, let's go.
来吧
Come on.
（完成模拟次数）
（总共反叛次数）
（99.8%匹配）